Guide to the Philip Agee Papers TAM.517
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
Philip Agee Papers
Bulk, 1965-2000
1948-2007
TAM.517
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
21.25 linear feet in 19 record cartons, 1 manuscript box, 1 photograph box, 1 oversize flat box, and 1 folder.
Philip Burnett Franklin Agee (1935–2008) was a Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) case officer and writer, best known as the author of Inside the Company: CIA Diary (1975), which identifed about 250 CIA officers, front companies and foreign agents then or previously working for the United States. Agee joined the CIA in 1957, and over the following decade had postings in Washington, D.C., Ecuador, Uruguay, and Mexico. After resigning from the Agency in 1968, he became a leading opponent of CIA practices. Exiled from the U.S., and expelled from Great Britain, he died in Cuba in January 2008. The collection contains: biographical materials, correspondence, datebooks, documents obtained under the FOIA Act, notably CIA documents, as well as FBI and State Department documents; legal materials from various cases in which Agee was the plaintiff; lectures and university teaching files; subject files, many relating to Latin American and other countries and to CIA activity in them, and some relating to his expulsion from Great Britain; published and unpublished writings by Agee; reviews of his work; and other writings about Agee.
Agee, Philip.
Historical/Biographical Note
Philip Burnett Franklin Agee (July 19, 1935–January 7, 2008) was a United States Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) case officer and writer. He is best known as the author of Inside the Company: CIA Diary (1975), first published in Britain because of legal problems in the U.S., which identifed about 250 officers, front companies and foreign agents working for or cooperating with the United States. Agee joined the CIA in 1957, and over the following decade had postings in Washington, D.C., Ecuador, Uruguay, and Mexico. After resigning from the Agency in 1968, he became a leading opponent of CIA practices. Agee also wrote Dirty Work: The CIA in Western Europe (1978), Dirty Work: The CIA in Africa (1979), and a biography, On the Run (1987). Agee's work inspired the founding of the Covert Action Information Bulletin, for which he also wrote. He was exiled from the U.S., for revealing classified information, via the revocation of his passport by the U.S. Department of State in 1979 while he was abroad (upheld by the U.S. Supreme Court in 1989). He was also pressured to leave Great Britain in 1977. He lectured throughout Western and Eastern Europe. Agee was also eventually expelled from Holland, France, West Germany, and Italy, and died in Cuba in January, 2008.
Agee was involved in several legal cases. Agee sued the United States Central Intelligence Agency, Federal Bureau of Investigation, National Security Agency, Department of State, and Department of Justice, seeking to obtain government documents under the Freedom of Information Act, and obtained numerous documents as a result of these complex legal proceedings that related to his former CIA employment, and to his investigative and writing activities. Agee also sued Barbara Bush,alleging that, in her Barbara Bush: Memoir (Scribner, 1994) she had falsely held him responsible for the death of Athens CIA Station Chief Richard Welch, assassinated in 1975. Agee also sued George Crile, Gust Avrakotos, Grove/Atlantic, the Atlantic Monthly Press, and Publishers Group West, claiming that Crile's book Charlie Wilson's War (Grove/Atlantic, 2003) falsely held him responsible for the death of Richard Welch.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Donated by Giselle Roberge Agee in 2009. The accession numbers associated with this collection are 2009.081 and 2011.064.
Scope and Contents note
The collection contains: biographical materials, photographs, correspondence, detailed datebooks; (U.S.) government documents obtained under the Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) -- principally CIA documents, as well as FBI and State Department documents; legal materials from various cases in which Agee was the plaintiff; lectures and university teaching files; subject files, many relating to Latin American and other countries and to the CIA's activities in relation to them, and some relating to his expulsion from Great Britain; writings by and about Agee; with clippings and clippings files throughout. The leading correspondent is Agee's attorney, Meliv L. Wulf; there is also correspondence with several publishers, with Noam Chomsky, Maurice Bishop, (revolutionary Prime Minister of Grenada from 1979-1983), Ilona Maria Lorenz (Fidel Castro's onetime lover, later hired by CIA to assassinate Castro), and publisher Lyle Stuart. The collection, in addition to documenting Agee's life, his career as a CIA agent and his subsequent activities to expose and oppose U.S. foreign intelligence activities and foreign policy goals, and legal cases in which he was involved, will also be of interest to the study of U.S. foreign intelligence activities and foreign policy, notably in relation to Latin America but also in Western Europe and elsewhere.
Arrangement
Organized into eleven series:
Series I, Biographical and Memorabilia
Series II, Datebooks
Series III, Correspondence
Subseries: A. Alphabetical
Subseries B. Chronological
Subseries C. Foreign Languages
Series IV, Government Documents
Series V, Legal Cases and Documents
Subseries: A. Agee v. Barbara Bush
Subseries B. Agee v. Ceorge Crile, et. al.
Subseries C. Agee v. United States
Subseries D. Agee v. U.S. Central Intelligence Agency, et. al.
Subseries E. Agee v. U.S. Dept. of State
Subseries F. Other Cases (Legal Documents from Cases of Interest to Agee)
Series VI, Subject Files
Subseries A. Countries: Latin America
Subseries B. Countries: Other
Subseries C. Expulsions
Subseries D. Individuals, Organizations, Topics
Series VII, University Lectures, Teaching and Research Files
Series VIII, Writings
Subseries: A. Published Writings
Subseries B. Unpublished Writings
Subseries C. Interviews
Subseries D. Speeches
Subseries E. Reviews of Agee's Writings
Subseries F. Writings about Agee
Subseries G. Writings by Others
Series IX, Oversized Clippings About Philip Agee
Series X, Audiocassettes and Computer Discs
Series XI: Photographs
Arranged alphabetically, unless otherwise specified.
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Researchers interested in using audiovisual materials in this collection (films, cassette tapes, VHS tapes, et cetera) must use a digitized copy, which we refer to as an access copy. Researchers may view an item’s original container, but the media themselves are not available for playback because of preservation concerns. Materials that already have already been digitized are noted in the collection’s finding aid and can be requested in our reading room; materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. These requests are free of charge and can be made in anticipation of your visit. The process typically takes four to six weeks. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@library.nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A librarian will respond to you with further information
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
In subseries VI-C, researchers must use the folder containing the copies of the fragile original clippings. For series X (Audiocassettes and Computer Discs), user copies must be made prior to use.
Agee, Philip.; Bush, Barbara, 1925-; Chomsky, Noam.; Grove Press.; Stuart, Lyle; United States. Central Intelligence Agency.; United States. Dept. of State.; United States. Freedom of Information Act.; Wulf, Melvin L.; Appointment books.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Deportation |z Great Britain.; Deportation |z United States.; Deportation.; Espionage, American |x History |y 20th century.; Espionage, American |z Latin America.; Espionage, American.; Government records.; Latin America |x Politics and government |y 20th century.; Lectures.; Legal documents.; Manuscripts for publication.; Teaching, Freedom of |z United States.; United States |x Foreign relations |z Latin America.
- Series I, Biographical and Memorabilia
  Scope and Content Note
  Series I, Biographical and Memorabilia (1975-1987) includes, in addition to Agee's typewriter (which was bugged by the CIA, and for which permisssion is required to view), includes the certificate of his marriage to Gysele Ingool, biographical profiles, business cards, certificates, clippings, itineraries and travel request forms, two plaques, and other memorabilia.
  - Typewriter Used by Philip Agee (Permission Required for Access) (Box 1)
  - Agreement between Ekkhardt Jurgens, Philip Agee and Verlag Druckerei Steidl, re Unheimlich zu Diensten (Uncanny Service), Aug 9, 1985 (Box 1A, Folder 1)
  - Agreement between Stonehill Publishing Company and Media Property Corporation re Inside the Company: CIA Diary, 1975 (Box 1A, Folder 2)
  - Application for and Denial of Passport at the U.S. Interests Section of the Embassy of Switzerland in Havana, Cuba, 2004-2006 (Box 1A, Folder 2A)
  - Biographies and Profiles (Published, Unpublished), 1987, undated (Box 1A, Folder 3)
  - Business Cards of Other Individuals, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 4)
  - Camargo-Seixas, Angela (Brazilian Leftist and Agee's Girlfriend, Early 1970s): Typescript by, Undated (Box 1A, Folder 4A)
  - Cartoon: "Free Me So I [CIA] Can Kill Again" [Tony Auth, autographed for Agee], undated (Box 1A, Folder 4B)
  - Certificate from the Internationalist Production Brigade, North American Section (Nicaragua Coffee Harvest), circa 1984 (Box 1A, Folder 5)
  - Identification Documents (Agee), 1953-1994 (Box 1A, Folder 5A)
  - Itinerary: Elissa, Mar 1989 (Box 1A, Folder 5B)
  - Itineraries (Agee), 1983, 1987 (Box 1A, Folder 5C)
  - Marriage to Gysele Ingool: Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 1A, Folder 6)
  - Notre Dame University: Clippings, Correspondence, Class Reunion, 1987-1994 (Box 1A, Folder 7)
  - Planned Tour to Australia and New Zealand, 1984-1987 (Box 1A, Folder 8)
  - Request to Consul of France for Permission to Enter France for His Wife's Tour, Feb 12, 1979 (Box 1A, Folder 9)
  - Plaque: From the Students of Indiana, Perdue, and Ohio State Universities, Spr 1994 (Box 1A, Folder 10)
  - Plaque: Massachusetts Institute of Technology Sloan School of Management Mexico--Cuba Trip, Mar 2003 (Box 1A, Folder 11)
- Series II, Correspondence
  Series II, Correspondence (1954-2006) is organized into three subseries: the alphabetical correspondence includes correspondence with his attorney and writing collaborator Melvin Wulf, various periodicals and publishers, including Lyle Stuart, Maurice Bishop (Prime Minister of Grenada (1979-83), the Social Democratic Party of Germany and its youth organization, Noam Chomsky and various progressive activists and authors around the world; the chronological correspondence subseries contain single or at most a few letters from diverse individuals of lesser reknown,; and the foreign languages subseries contains correspondence, in German and to a lesser degree, Spanish, and concerns Agee's literary and political activities and connections. Note that Melvin Wulf also sometimes appears as a correspondent or author in series IV, Government Documents, and V, Legal Cases and Documents.
  - Subseries II-A, Correspondence, Alphabetical
    - Allen, Lili-Florine (Anti-Violent Continental Army, Berkeley, CA), 1961-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Betz, Charles (Letter from The Progressive Student Organization, includes clippings), 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Bishop, Maurice (Prime Minister of Grenada), Jun 3, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Brandon Book Publishers, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Brockman-Wiese, Hartmut Jacobi, Hartmut Scharmer, Annette Voges, Rechtsanwaltinnen und Rechtsanwalte (Lawyers), 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Canadian Embassy, Feb. 11, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Central American Resource Center, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Center for National Security Studies, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7a)
    - Chomsky, Noam, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Freney, Denis (Australian Communist journalist), 1954 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Frias, Adan Chavez: Venezuela's Embassador in Cuba, Nov 18, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Grant, Lawrence (Solicitor at Seifert, Sedley, & Co.), 1977-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - IVG Immobilien (Property Agency [German], Apartment Rent), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Kjolseth, Rolf (Sociology Professor), 1976-1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Larson, Rodney (Transnational Features Service, International Labor Organization), 1974-1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Lorenz, Ilona Maria (Castro's lover - later hired by CIA to assassinate Castro, includes clippings), 1960-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Los Angeles Times, Oct 4, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Mother Jones Magazine's Response to Agee's Manuscript, Sep 26, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Nicaragua, 1982, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Owanisian-Wagner, Wendy and Marie (Whiteside Newsweek editor, re: West Germany's Secret Service), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Papoutsakis, Christos (editor of Greek dissent magazine Anti), 1977-1986 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Red Bass, 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Rislak, Jukka (re: Rama Swarup Indian Freedom Fighter and the CIA), 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Sozialdemokratische Partei Deutschlands - Jugendsozialisten (Social Democrats of Germany - Youth Socialists), 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Sozialistische Deutsche Arbeitjugend Bundesvorstand (Socialist German Youth Worker's Federal Committee, West German Youth Organization), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Sozialistische Jugend Deutschlands, Die Falken (Socialist Youth Germany, The Falcons, West German Youth Organization), 1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Speak Out!, Mar 17, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Straight Arrow Publishers (San Francisco, CA), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Stuart, Lyle, Mario Sartori (Publisher and editor of On the Run), 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Tri Star Pictures, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Von Berenberg-Gossler, Sigrid, Rechtsanwaltin (Lawyer), 1983-1987 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Wolf, Louis ( Covert Action Information Bulletin Editor), 1974-1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1977-1981 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1987-1989 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Wulf, Melvin L., 1994-1996 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Subseries II-B, Correspondence, Chronological
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1982-May 1982 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1982-Dec 1982 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1983-Feb 1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, Mar 1983-Aug 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1983-Dec 1983 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1984-May 1984 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1984-Sep 1984 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Correspondence, Oct 1984-Dec 1984 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1985-Mar 1985 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Correspondence, Apr 1985-Dec 1985 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1987-May 1987 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1987-Aug 1987 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Sep 1987-Dec 1987 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1988-May 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jun 1988-Jul 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Aug 1988-Dec 1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan 1989-Apr 1989 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, May 1989-Dec 1989 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1993-1996, 2006 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Subseries II-C, Correspondence, Foreign Languages
    - Correspondence (German), 1983-1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence (German), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence (German), 1986-1988, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (German), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Spanish), 1982 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Spanish), 1983-1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Series III, Datebooks
  Series III, Datebooks (1975-2007) contains bound volumes containing both appointments and notes, some detailed. The datebooks combine features of ddate/appointment books with those of diaries and notebooks. Included is contextual information and notes about appointments, research notes and political ccommentary, sometimes commingled.
  - Datebooks, undated, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Datebooks, 1976, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Datebooks, 1978, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Datebooks, 1980,1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Datebooks, 1982, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Datebooks, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Datebooks, 1985, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Datebooks, 1987, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Datebooks, 1989, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Datebooks, 1991, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Datebooks, 1993, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Datebooks, 1995, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Datebooks, 1997, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Datebooks, 1999, 200 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Datebooks, 2001, 2004 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Datebooks, 2006, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Series IV, Government Documents
  Series IV, Government Documents (1950-1989), contains materials obtained under the Freedom of Information Act, the largest number from the CIA, but also including documents from the Department of State (individual files on countries around the world, including several on Great Britain), the Department of Justice, and the FBI, and several small files from other agencies. The CIA files and Department of Justice files include, in addition to files requested by Agee about various activities of these agencies, also include files about Agee, and about the contested nature of the FOIA process. The FBI files are principally lists of deleted materials, i.e., materials not released, but there is also a list of released documents and well as some documents themselves.
  - National Security Agency/Central Security Service, 1978-1981 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - United States International Agency, Feb 1, 1980-Jun 1, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - United States International Development Cooperation Agency: Agency for International Development, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - United States Senate: Committee on Foreign Relations, Office of Congressional Liasion, Feb 1975-June 1975 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - US CIA: Activities in the Soviet Union, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - US CIA: Administration of the Freedom of Information and Annual Report of Calendar Year 1978, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - US CIA: Alleged Assassination Plots Involving Foreign Leaders - An Interim Report of the Select Committee to Study Governmental Operations, Nov 1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - US CIA: Assignments, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - US CIA: Biographical Files and Memorandums on Case, 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - US CIA: Biographical Files and Memorandums on Case (2), 1960s-1970s (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - US CIA: Clippings, Book Chapters, 1974, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - US CIA: Confiscated Letters Written By Agee, 1971, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - US CIA: Correspondence, 1976, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - US CIA: Covert Action Information Bulletin, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - US CIA: Exposure of Agent Richard Welch and Other Agents, 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - US CIA: Financial Records, 1960s (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - US CIA: Hiring Files (Personal History Security Approval, Declaration of Appointment), 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - US CIA: Information and Record Management (Agency Information Security Program Handbook), Nov 28, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - US CIA: Inside the Company, 1974-1976 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - US CIA: Jane W. Agee Secrecy Agreement and Other Related Files, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - US CIA: List of Deleted and Exempt Categories, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - US CIA: List of Released Documents (Includes Description of Withheld Portions), Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - US CIA: Lists of Denied Documents with Explanations, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - US CIA: Lists of Requested Documents, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - US CIA: Memorandum About Meeting Agee's Father, 1970s (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - US CIA: Memorandums Re: Possible Prosecution of Agee, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - US CIA: "On Company Business" Proposal for a Documentary Film on the CIA with Agee, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - US CIA: Open Letter Published in Uruguayan Leftist Publication "Marche", 1970s (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - US CIA: Performance Evaluations, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - US CIA: Press Coverage on Agee's Case, 1976-1980 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - US CIA: "Proposicion Para El Estable Cimiento De Us Programa De Desarrollo Deportivo" (Resumen), 1980 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - US CIA: Psychological Assessment, early 1970s (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - US CIA: Public Activities (Interviews, Speeches, etc.), 1970s (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - US CIA: Relationship with Cuban Agents, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - US CIA: Requests for and Notifications of Personnel Action, 1950s-1960s (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - US CIA: Requests of Confidential Documents "Service Request Slips" and "Routing and Transmittal Slips", 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - US CIA: Resignation, 1968, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - US CIA: Resignation from CIA: "Termination Secrecy Oath", Nov 22, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - US CIA: Secrecy Agreement, Jul 1, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - US CIA: Task Force Report on Greater CIA Openness, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - US CIA: Termination of Secrecy Oath, Aug 26, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - US CIA: Training at the Agency, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - US CIA: Travel Itineraries and Vouchers, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - US CIA and FBI List of Released Documents (Includes Description of Withheld Portions), Undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - US Defence Intelligence Agency: Correspondence and Released Documents, 1975-1979 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - US Department of Justice: Civil Rights Division, 1975-1978 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - US Department of Justice: Civil Rights Division, 1975-1981 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - US Department of Justice. Civil Rights Division: Correspondence, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - US Department of Justice. Civil Rights Division: Inventory of Records, 1977-1981 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - US Department of Justice. Criminal Division: Correspondence (1), 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - US Department of Justice. Criminal Division: Correspondence (2), 1977-1985 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - US Department of Justice. Criminal Division: CRM/PA No. 3258 Central Index and Associate Records (Released Sep 11, 1981), 1976-1976, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - US Department of Justice. Drug Enforcement Administration, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - US Department of Justice. Internal Security Section, 1975, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - US Department of Justice. Office of Legal Counsel: Correspondence, Jan 9, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - US Department of Justice. Office of Privacy and Information Appeals (OPIA): Correspondence, 1987-1989 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - US Department of Justice. Office of Privacy and Information Appeals (OPIA): Released Documents (1-10), 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - US Department of Justice. Office of Privacy and Information Appeals (OPIA): Revealed Documents (11-19), 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)